- ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
- Dawn, it's so cool you made it to the top of the rock wall
Dawn，你昨天以创纪录的时间登上了攀岩墙的顶端，真是太酷了。
in record time yesterday.
你怎么没在FaceShack上发帖子呢？
How come you didn't post about it on FaceShack?
哦，我不喜欢在网上炫耀。
- Oh, I don't like to brag online.
我喜欢当面炫耀。
I like to brag in person.
那么谁有四个大拇指，还征服了攀岩墙呢？
So who has four thumbs and rocks the rock wall?
就是这个女孩！
This girl!
啊！她有四个大拇指！
- Ah! She has four thumbs!
是的，其中两个是Mae的。
- Yeah, and two of them are Mae's.
你拿走了Mae的大拇指？
- You took Mae's thumbs? - Hello?
- 你拿了Mae的拇指？ - 喂？
- Ah! And her head?
- 啊！还有她的头？
[laughter]
[笑声]
- I don't think it had the impact we thought it would.
- 我觉得这效果没我们想的那么大。
- Well, I thought your thumbs were great.
- 呃，我觉得你的拇指很棒。
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Ricky Harper! What's up?
- Ricky Harper！最近怎么样？
- Just you, Cash Money!
- 就你，Cash Money！
- You know them?
- 你认识他们？
- More like they know me.
- 更像是他们认识我。
- And they know you too?
- 他们也认识你吗？
- We're wiggling fingers, aren't we?
- 我们不是在挥手吗？
- Yo, Harps! - 'Zup, Zayn?
- 哟，哈普斯！ - 咋了，赞恩？
- Will you come meet my girlfriend?
- 你能来见见我女朋友吗？
- Sure thing, Zayniac.
- 当然可以，赞尼克。
- Okay, what is happening?
- 好吧，这是怎么回事？
- This is very confusing.
- 这太让人困惑了。
- I know what's going on here.
- 我知道这里发生了什么。
See, Ricky added an "iac" to "Zayn"
你看，里基在“赞恩”后面加了个“iac”
to make what's known as a "nickname."
来创造一个所谓的“昵称”。
- Not that. We've only been at this school for a few weeks.
- 不是那个。我们才来这所学校几周。
How is Ricky getting so many points and wiggle waves?
里基是怎么得到这么多积分和摇摆波浪的？
- Oh.
- 哦。
Yeah, no idea.
是啊，不知道。
- Hey, guys.
- 嘿，伙计们。
Dawn, did you get my text about Glee Club rehearsal?
Dawn，你收到我关于Glee Club排练的短信了吗？
- Yeah, and check this out.
- 收到了，你看这个。
When I got it, I was also texting Mae
当我收到短信时，我还在用另一只手在平板上给Mae发短信，
on a tablet with my other hand,
所以我跟我妈说，我就像，
so I said to my mom, I'm like,
嘿，看，我是双手机达人！
"Hey, look, I'm ambi-text-rous!"
嘿，看，我是左右开弓的！
- Dawn, that happened to Ricky.
Dawn，Ricky也遇到过这种情况。
- He's the one who said "ambi-text-rous."
他就是那个说‘左右开弓’的人。
- What? Ricky didn't say that.
什么？Ricky没说过那个词。
He's barely "text-rous."
他连‘单手发短信’都勉强。
- Pretty sure he did.
我很确定他说过。
He posted it on his FaceShack page.
他在他的FaceShack页面上发过。
- He even hashtagged it "RickyLife."
他甚至还加了#RickyLife的标签。
So it's definitely Ricky's life.
所以这绝对是Ricky的生活。
"Ambi-text-rous"!
‘左右开弓’！
[both laugh]
[两人都笑了]
- How could he do this?
他怎么能这样做？
He posted my story like it happened to him.
他把我的故事贴出来，好像发生在他身上一样。
Wait, did you guys know about this?
等等，你们知道这件事吗？
- No, we're not FaceShack buddies with Ricky.
不，我们和Ricky不是FaceShack的好友。
- Yeah, we live with him.
是的，我们和他住在一起。
We don't want to relive it online.
我们不想在网上重温这些。
- Yeah, well, maybe you should,
是啊，也许你们应该，
because I'm not the only one he stole from.
因为我不他唯一偷窃的对象。
Look.
看。
- He posted my cookies! [knocking]
- 他把我做的饼干发到网上了！[敲门声]
Ugh, and he called them "Rickerdoodles."
啊，他还把它们叫做“Rickerdoodles”。
Their rightful name are "Nickerdoodles"!
它们真正的名字应该是“Nickerdoodles”！
- Forget your cookies.
- 别管你的饼干了。
Yesterday, he posted a hair care tip
昨天，他发了一个我发明的护发小贴士。看。
I invented. Look.
“把你的梳子放在冰箱里。
"Keep your brush in the freezer.
这样你的头发就会有冰淇淋的味道。”
It makes your hair smell like ice cream."
这个点子是我想到的。来。
I thought of that. Here.
闻闻看。
Go ahead, smell.
不闻算了。 - 你的损失。薄荷巧克力碎片味。
- Pass. - Your loss.
- 不感兴趣。 - 你吃亏了。
Mint chocolate chip.
薄荷巧克力碎片。
- Who does he think he is, stealing our stuff?
- 他以为他是谁，偷我们的东西？
That should be us taking happy selfies
应该是我们和一大堆新朋友自拍，
with tons of new friends.
而不是他！
Not him!
- 什么？看他刚发了什么。
- What? Look what he just posted.
“猜猜谁有12个拇指，昨天攀岩创了纪录？
"Guess who's got 12 thumbs and set a record
“就是这家伙！”
"climbing the rock wall yesterday?
所有人: 那家伙。
This guy!"
[欢快音乐]
all: That guy.
就是他。
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- ♪ ♪
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ - ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ - ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪
[cheerful music]
[欢快音乐]
- Okay, we all know what we're gonna say
- 好吧，我们都知道要对#RickyLife先生说什么，对吧？
to Mr. #RickyLife, right?
- 对。 - 明白了。
- Right. - Got it.
- Hey, you might want to leave.
- 嘿，你可能想离开。
I know you don't like confrontation.
我知道你不喜欢冲突。
- [barks] - Okay.
- [吠叫] - 好吧。
But don't say I didn't warn you.
但别说我没警告你。
- Warn who about what?
- 警告谁关于什么？
- Just talkin' about stuff people post on FaceShack.
- 只是谈论人们在FaceShack上发布的东西。
- Oh. Now, kids.
- 哦。现在，孩子们。
You have to be very careful
你们在FaceShack上发布内容时必须非常小心。
what you post on FaceShack.
- Tom! What did you just post on FaceShack?
汤姆！你刚刚在FaceShack上发了什么？
- Excuse me one second.
请稍等一下。
[laughter]
[笑声]
Oh! It's a cute video of Squishy, huh?
哦！是一个可爱的Squishy视频，对吧？
Phew, I thought I was in trouble.
呼，我还以为我惹麻烦了。
- Uh, you will be if you don't take it down.
呃，如果你不撤下来，你就会有麻烦。
- What? Why? It's a great promotion for the store. Sales are up.
什么？为什么？这对商店是个很好的宣传。销售额上升了。
- Listen to what I'm saying
听我说
in the background.
在背景里。
Ugh, Mom, I'm dreading it.
唉，妈妈，我真不想面对。
Tom's mom is sending us
汤姆的妈妈每年都会给我们送
her annual chocolate cake
周年纪念的巧克力蛋糕。
for our anniversary.
不不不，当然，她亲手做很贴心，
No, no, no, sure, it's sweet that she made it,
但她没必要吃它！
but she doesn't have to eat it!
敲门声 太可怕了！
[knocking] It's horrible!
连浣熊都不会吃。
Even a raccoon wouldn't eat it.
不，说真的。
No, no, seriously.
去年我把蛋糕放在外面，
I left it outside last year,
浣熊都不吃。
and a raccoon would not eat it.
呃！
Ugh!
- Wait, you gave our cake to the raccoons?
等等，你把我们的蛋糕给浣熊了？
- Well, I tried to,
嗯，我试过给它们，
but they just looked at me like--
但它们只是看着我，好像——
[hisses]
（嘶嘶声）
Take the video down.
把视频删掉。
- My mom's not even on FaceShack.
我妈妈甚至不在FaceShack上。
- Yes, but other relatives are.
是的，但其他亲戚在。
It's gonna get back to her.
这迟早会传到她那里。
Please just take it down.
请把它删掉吧。
- Oh, but people love the pooch, Anne.
哦，但是人们喜欢这只小狗，安妮。
They just want to eat him up.
他们只是想把他吃掉。
- [hisses]
（嘶嘶声）
- Well, well, well.
好吧，好吧，好吧。
- Wait, I thought we were each gonna do one of the wells.
等等，我以为我们每个人都要说一个'好吧'。
- No, we decided Dawn should say all of them.
不，我们决定让Dawn说所有的'好吧'。
- Well, wait, so what do I say?
好吧，等等，那我说什么？
- You say, "Where have you been?"
你说，'你去哪儿了？'
- Got it.
明白了。
Where have been you?
你去哪儿了？
Dang it!
该死！
- Ricky, why have you been posting all of our things
Ricky，你为什么把我们所有的东西都发上去，
like they were yours?
好像是你自己的一样？
- Yeah, so here's the thing.
是啊，事情是这样的。
I was posting stuff about my own life--
我是在发关于我自己生活的内容——
math grades, knitting,
数学成绩，编织，
correcting people's grammar and such--
纠正别人的语法等等——
but for some reason, I wasn't getting a lot of knocks
但不知为何，我并没有收到很多
on my FaceShack door,
在FaceShack上的敲门声，
so I stole some of your lives.
所以我偷了一些你的生活。
- Ricky, you can't just steal other people's lives.
Ricky, 你不能就这样偷走别人的生活。
- Well, you weren't posting about them,
嗯，你又没发关于他们的帖子，
and if you didn't post about it, did it really happen?
如果你不发帖，那事情真的发生过吗？
all: Yes!
是的！
- Sorry, but you snooze, you lose.
抱歉，但机会稍纵即逝。
No posting, no boasting.
不发帖，就没得炫耀。
No tagging, no bragging.
不标记，就没得吹嘘。
No shares, who cares?
不分享，谁在乎？
- Stop it!
住手！
Stop rhyming, stop lying,
别再押韵了，别再撒谎了，
stop stealing, and stop posting!
停止偷窃，停止发布！
- Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
是啊，那是不可能的。
- Why not?
为什么不？
- [evilly] 'Cause I like it.
因为我喜欢。
- Okay, that was weird.
好吧，那有点奇怪。
- Sorry, but I started getting all those knocks,
对不起，但我开始得到那些敲门声，
and it feels so good.
感觉太好了。
- Look, if you don't stop stealing our lives,
听着，如果你不停止偷窃我们的生活，
we're gonna stop giving you lives to steal.
我们就不再给你生活去偷了。
So from now on, whenever we're around you,
所以从现在起，每当我们在你身边，
we're gonna be the most boring, uninteresting kids in the world.
我们会成为世界上最无聊、最无趣的孩子。
- How are you gonna do that?
- 你们打算怎么做？
- [evilly] Just you wait.
- [邪恶地]等着瞧吧。
- Oh, that is weird.
- 哦，那真是奇怪。
What are you doing?
你们在干什么？
- I'm going to do math.
- 我要做数学。
- I am going to knit.
- 我要织毛衣。
- I'm going to make your grammar gooder.
- 我要让你的语法更好。
- I'm going to do this. [camera shutter clicks]
- 我要做这个。[相机快门声]
- Go ahead. Post away.
- 尽管来吧。尽情发帖。
And see how many knocks you get now.
看看你现在能得到多少敲门声。
- Look how many knocks he's getting now!
- 看他现在得到了多少敲门声！
- "The other Quads look up to me so much,
- “其他四胞胎非常仰慕我，
"they've started to dress like me.
“他们开始模仿我的穿着。
Guess it's #DressLikeRickyDay."
猜今天是#像Ricky一样穿衣日。”
- Yeah, like anybody would ever do that.
- 是啊，好像有人会这么做似的。
[dramatic music]
I've had this nightmare.
我做过这个噩梦。
They're gonna bore us to sleep,
他们会让我们无聊到睡着，
then knit us into cocoons.
然后把我们织进茧里。
- Then we hatch into new Rickys with wings.
- 然后我们孵化成带有翅膀的新Ricky。
- You've had the same nightmare?
- 你也做过同样的噩梦吗？
- Haven't we all?
- 我们不都做过吗？
This stops right now.
这必须立刻停止。
- Ooh, looks like your little plan backfired.
- 哦，看来你的小计划适得其反了。
- I can't believe you tricked the entire school
- 真不敢相信你骗了整个学校
into thinking that you're cool.
让他们以为你很酷。
- It's the power of the Internet.
- 这就是互联网的力量。
I'm a social influencer.
我是个社交影响者。
- Yeah, well, we're gonna tell everyone the truth.
- 是啊，我们打算告诉所有人真相。
- Go ahead and try, but let me Rick-splain something to you.
- 尽管试试看，但让我给你解释一下。
Once you build a strong personal brand online,
一旦你在网上建立了强大的个人品牌，
people trust it.
人们就会信任它。
They'll believe anything I say.
他们会相信我说的任何话。
- Anything? - Yeah.
- 任何话？ - 是的。
I can make up any dumb catchphrase,
我可以编造任何愚蠢的口号，
and with one post,
只需一个帖子，
my followers will start saying it.
我的追随者就会开始说它。
Like, uh...
比如，呃...
"You ain't got the bread."
“你没那本事。”
- "You ain't got the bread"?
- “You ain't got the bread”?
That doesn't even mean anything.
这根本没有任何意义。
[phone chimes] - They don't know that.
- 他们不知道。
- Hey, where are your Ricky sweaters?
- 嘿，你的Ricky毛衣呢？
- Oh, yeah, we're not doing that.
- 哦，对，我们不搞那个了。
- Psh. You ain't got the bread.
- 哼，你没那资本。
- I think that Rick-speaks for itself.
- 我觉得Rick的话已经说明一切了。
[knocking]
Oh, and so do those sweet, sweet knocks.
哦，那些甜美的敲门声也是。
So many, it's almost ob-knock-sious.
太多了，几乎到了烦人的地步。
[laughing]
[笑]
- He is out of control.
- 他失控了。
We have to do something.
我们必须采取行动。
- Well, if they aren't going to listen to us,
- 好吧，如果他们不听我们的，
then maybe we need to create somebody more popular
那么也许我们需要创造一个比Ricky更受欢迎的在线人物，
than Ricky online that they will listen to.
他们会听从的。
- So we can steal all of his knocks
- 这样我们就可以偷走他所有的敲门声
and take him down a notch. - Exactly.
并让他降一降热度。 - 没错。
- But it would need to be an untraceable account
- 但这需要是一个无法追踪的账号
so Ricky won't know it's us.
这样Ricky就不会知道是我们。
- We'd need some type of computer whiz.
- 我们需要某种电脑高手。
- But we don't have a whiz.
- 但我们没有高手。
- And we ain't got the bread either.
- 而且我们也没钱。
- But we do have the pie.
- 但我们有派。
So, how's your pie, Mae? - What do you want?
那么，你的派怎么样，Mae？ - 你想要什么？
I know there's no such thing as free pie.
我知道没有免费的派这回事。
- Okay, you know how you're like a computer whiz?
- 好吧，你知道你就像个电脑高手吗？
- I'm not like one. I am one.
- 我不是像一个。我就是一个。
- Well, we need you to help us create
- 那么，我们需要你帮我们创建
an untraceable FaceShack account.
一个无法追踪的FaceShack账户。
- To destroy Ricky.
- 为了摧毁Ricky。
- So he ain't got the bread.
- 这样他就没钱了。
- What does that mean? - Nothing!
- 那是什么意思？ - 没什么！
That's why we have to destroy him.
这就是为什么我们必须摧毁他。
- Look, Ricky has this FaceShack account,
- 看，Ricky有一个FaceShack账户，
and he's stealing all of our stories,
他正在窃取我们所有的故事，
and he's completely out of control.
他已经完全失控了。
- And you think me creating a fake profile
- 而你认为我创建一个比他更受欢迎的假账号
that's more popular than his is gonna take him down?
就能把他打倒吗？
- Yeah! Mae, we have this whole online persona planned out.
- 是的！Mae，我们已经计划好了一个完整的在线身份。
- We even have a cool name: "BoCo Yolo."
- 我们甚至有个酷炫的名字：“BoCo Yolo”。
- "BoCo"? - Yeah, as in Boulder, Colorado.
- “BoCo”？ - 是的，就像博尔德，科罗拉多。
- See, no one will ever know who BoCo is
- 看，没人会知道BoCo是谁
because Boco's face will always be... shrouded in mystery.
因为BoCo的脸永远会被...笼罩在神秘之中。
- And a hoodie.
- 还有一件连帽衫。
- All this sounds great, but...
- 这一切听起来都很棒，但是...
I'm out.
我退出。
Now, back to my pie.
现在，回到我的派上。
- No more pie.
- 没有派了。
- Sorry,
- 对不起，
but creating an account just to chase knocks
但仅仅为了追逐敲门声而创建账户
is dangerous.
是危险的。
Before you know it, all you care about hearing
在你意识到之前，你所关心的
is the next knock.
只是下一个敲门声。
Then the next one. And the next one.
然后是下一个。再下一个。
Where's my next knock?
我的下一个敲门声在哪里？
[yelling] Where?
[大喊]在哪里？
- Give her the pie back. - Okay.
把派还给她。好的。
Are you talking from experience, Mae?
你是在根据经验说话吗，Mae？
- No, I just wanted my pie back.
不，我只是想要我的派回来。
But trust me, from everything I've read,
但相信我，从我读过的所有资料来看，
you don't want to go down that road.
你不会想走那条路的。
- But Ricky is headed down that road,
- 但Ricky正朝着那条路走，
and he needs our help.
他需要我们的帮助。
Come on, Mae.
来吧，Mae。
Help us help him.
帮我们帮他。
- I'm sorry.
- 对不起。
There's no way I can do this.
我没办法这么做。
Now can I finish my pie, please?
现在我可以继续吃我的派了吗？
- Sure, Mae.
- 当然，Mae。
You finish your pie.
你吃完你的派。
- Thank you.
谢谢。
What's this?
这是什么？
Why is Ricky holding my cat?
为什么Ricky抱着我的猫？
- Oh, he posted that yesterday.
哦，他昨天发的。
And he hashtagged it "the purrr-fect couple."
他还加了标签“完美情侣”。
- But Debbie and I are the purrr-fect couple!
但Debbie和我才是完美情侣！
He may have the bread now,
他现在可能有了面包，
but when I'm through with him,
但等我搞定他，
he's gonna be toast!
他就会变成烤面包！
- ♪ ♪
♪ ♪
- Hey, everyone!
嘿，大家好！
'Zup, Zayn?
咋了，Zayn？
Classic Zayniac, am I right?
典型的Zayniac，对吧？
Good morning, ladies.
早上好，女士们。
Classic ladies! [laughs nervously]
典型的女士们！[紧张地笑]
[laughter]
[笑声]
So, looking at FaceShack, huh?
所以，在看FaceShack，嗯？
- Yeah. This BoCo Yolo kid is blowin' up.
是啊。这个BoCo Yolo小子现在火得不得了。
- BoCo who, now?
BoCo谁，现在？
- BoCo Yolo!
He's trending like crazy.
他现在火得不得了。
- Probably because he posts cool stuff like this.
- 可能是因为他发了像这样的酷东西。
[knocking]
[敲门]
- I mean, that's okay,
- 我是说，那还不错，
but did you see
但你看到
what the Rickinator posted this morning?
今天早上Rickinator发的东西了吗？
- It was just a FaceShack Memory.
- 那只是一个FaceShack的回忆。
From two days ago.
从两天前。
- Yeah, we get it. You're friends with a cat.
- 是啊，我们知道了。你和一只猫是朋友。
- BoCo's so cool.
BoCo太酷了。
But that hoodie always hides his face.
但那件连帽衫总是遮住他的脸。
I wonder what he looks like.
我想知道他长什么样。
- Rumor has it he goes to this school.
有传言说他来这所学校。
- I go to this school...
我在这所学校...
- It's working.
这招奏效了。
Everybody loves BoCo.
大家都喜欢BoCo。
- And they're tired of Ricky.
而且他们已经厌倦了Ricky。
- Looks like BoCo's got the bread now.
看来BoCo现在掌握了局面。
[all laugh evilly]
（大家都邪恶地笑）
[laughter]
[笑声]
♪ ♪
- Tom, you didn't take down the cake video.
- Tom, 你没把蛋糕视频撤下来。
- Oh, I wanted to, Anne,
- 哦，我想撤的，Anne,
but then all these customers started coming in,
但是后来所有这些顾客开始涌进来，
and did you see how many knocks it got?
你看到它获得了多少次点击吗？
- Oh, yeah, I did, I did and one of them is from your mother!
- 哦，是的，我看到了，而且其中一次是来自你妈妈的！
- Huh. I guess she is on FaceShack.
- 哼。我猜她在FaceShack上。
- Okay.
- 好吧。
- Look, if she gave the video a knock,
- 看，如果她给视频点了赞，
she must like it.
她一定喜欢。
- No, not necessarily.
- 不，不一定。
A knock could mean anything.
一个敲击可以意味着任何事情。
It could be a sarcastic knock.
可能是讽刺的敲击。
- There's no such thing as a sarcastic knock.
- 没有所谓的讽刺敲击。
- That profile pic of you in a sombrero.
- 你戴着宽边帽的那个头像。
Knock, knock. - [gasps] Anne!
敲，敲。 - [喘气] 安妮！
You commented I was your amigo!
你评论说我成了你的朋友！
- That was an autocorrect from "OMG!"
- 那是从“OMG！”自动纠正过来的。
- Oh! Here comes Ricky.
- 哦！瑞奇来了。
- He's probably feeling the burn.
他可能感到压力山大。
- Yeah, we helped him pretty hard.
是啊，我们让他挺难受的。
- Hey, guys!
嘿，伙计们！
all: Hey...
嘿...
- Okay, why is he so happy?
好吧，他为什么这么开心？
- We have a problem.
我们有个问题。
He's posting again.
他又开始发帖了。
[knocking]
敲门声
- What?
什么？
He never crowd-surfed at Chellapalooza!
他从未在Chellapalooza音乐节上做过人群冲浪！
- The Internet doesn't know that,
互联网不知道这一点，
and look how many knocks he's getting.
看看他得到了多少次敲击。
- Now he's just making stuff up!
现在他只是在编造东西！
- Isn't that what we're doing?
那不正是我们在做的吗？
- Yes, but we're doing it to help him.
是的，但我们这样做是为了帮助他。
- Okay, but we need to start making up some better stuff
好吧，但我们需要开始编造一些更好的东西
so we can take that little fake FaceShacker down.
这样我们才能把那个小假脸黑客打倒。
- He got more knocks than BoCo's last post, Mae!
他得到的敲击比BoCo上次帖子还多，Mae！
- Oh, no, no, no.
哦，不，不，不。
No one gets more knocks than BoCo.
没有人能比BoCo得到更多的敲击。
This fake posting's about to get real.
这个假帖子即将变得真实。
"Cute human flag, but check this one out."
“可爱的人旗，”“但看看这个。”
[knocking] - No time for petting zoo pics.
敲击声 - “没时间看宠物园的图片。”
I'm too busy getting my double black belt.
“我正忙着获得我的双黑带。”
[knocking] - "Only a double?
敲击声 - “只有双黑带？”
I just got my triple... from a ninja."
“我刚从一位忍者那里获得了三黑带...”
[knocking] - Whatever.
敲击声 - “随便吧。”
Karate is so last week.
“空手道已经是上周的事了。”
Now I get my kicks eating a hot dog...
“现在我通过吃热狗来获得刺激...”
while walking on a high wire.
“同时走钢丝。”
[knocking] - "Adorable.
敲门声
"But check me out carrying a real dog...
“可爱极了。“但是看看我，抱着一只真狗...
while walking on hot coals."
在火炭上行走。”
[knocking]
敲门声
- BoCo Yolo is hurting the Rickinator.
BoCo Yolo正在给Rickinator造成伤害。
[gasps]
（倒吸气）
- Sorry, Ricky.
对不起，Ricky。
This BoCo kid is obviously good.
这个BoCo孩子显然很厉害。
You can't compete with that.
你无法与之竞争。
Our advice is just let it go.
我们的建议是放手吧。
- Yeah, there's no shame. - Can't win 'em all, buddy.
- 是的，没什么可羞愧的。 - 不可能赢得所有比赛，伙计。
- Yeah, we're just trying to help.
- 是的，我们只是想帮忙。
- Help? Even after I stole your lives?
- 帮忙？即使在我偷了你们的机会之后？
- Hey, we just don't like to see the Rickinator hurting.
- 嘿，我们只是不想看到Rickinator受伤。
- Yeah, forgive and forget.
- 是的，原谅并忘记。
- Forgive and forget?
- 原谅并忘记？
They never forgive or forget.
他们从不原谅或忘记。
♪ ♪
- Oh, hey.
- 哦，嘿。
Is your mom's cake here yet?
你妈妈的蛋糕到了吗？
I bought some milk to get it down.
我买了些牛奶来帮助下咽。
- [laughs] Not yet.
还没到。
- Good.
那就好。
It's usually here by now.
通常这时候已经到了。
Wait a minute.
等一下。
It's usually here by now!
通常这时候已经到了！
Oh...
哦...
I knew it. I knew it.
我就知道，我就知道。
She heard me in the video, Tom.
她在视频里听到我了，汤姆。
She definitely heard me,
她肯定听到了，
and now she's not sending it!
而现在她不发过来了！
I mean, I didn't like the cake,
我是说，我不喜欢那蛋糕，
but I liked getting the cake,
但我喜欢收到蛋糕，
and now we're not getting the cake!
现在我们收不到蛋糕了！
- So now you want to get the cake?
所以你现在想收到蛋糕？
[laughter]
[笑声]
- Oh...
哦...
No, of course I don't want the cake.
不，当然我不想要那蛋糕。
But I don't not want it like this!
但我不是以这种方式不想要它！
Don't you understand?
你难道不明白吗？
- I don't not not understand.
我并非不理解。
- Okay.
好吧。
That cake was an expression
那块蛋糕是她对我们爱的表达。
of her love for us.
对我！
For me!
而现在那份爱已经消失了，汤姆。
And now the love is gone, Tom.
[敲门声]
[knock on door]
有人拿到了周年纪念蛋糕！
- Someone got an anniversary cake!
[兴奋地呻吟] - 谢谢你。
- [groans excitedly] - Thank you.
嘿，看我妈妈给你带了什么！
Hey, look what my mom got you!
[咯咯笑] 是的！她爱我，汤姆。她爱我！
- [giggling] Yes! She loves me, Tom.
是的！她爱我，Tom。
She loves me!
她爱我！
Oh, yes!
哦，是的！
[groaning] She loves me, Tom.
她爱我，Tom。
Ugh... she loves me!
呃...她爱我！
Milk!
牛奶！
Ah! Ah! Milk! Milk!
啊！啊！牛奶！牛奶！
- I'll go to the store.
我去商店。
- Hurry!
快点！
♪ ♪
- Hey, guys.
嘿，伙计们。
So I've been thinking
所以我一直在想
a lot about what you said,
你说的那些话，
and maybe I did get a little carried away.
也许我确实有点过头了。
So I'm quitting FaceShack.
所以我要退出FaceShack。
- Really?
真的吗？
- Yeah.
是的。
No more posting lies.
不再发布谎言。
No more chasing knocks.
不再追逐点赞。
From now on, I'm just giving them.
从现在起，我只给予。
And this one's for you, Boco Yolo.
这个是给你的，Boco Yolo。
[simultaneous knocking] Aha!
[同时敲门声] 啊哈！
I knew you guys were BoCo Yolo!
我就知道你们是BoCo Yolo！
Forgive and forget, huh?
原谅并忘记，是吧？
Oh, I'm gonna forget... to forgive!
哦，我会忘记...去原谅！
- Ricky, we were just trying to help you.
- Ricky，我们只是想帮你。
- Were you? Were you really?
- 是吗？真的吗？
Or were you just trying to get a taste of those sweet knocks?
还是你们只是想尝尝那些甜美的敲门声？
- No. - Who cares about knocks?
- 不是。 - 谁在乎敲门声？
- Yeah, we can stop posting whenever we want.
- 是的，我们可以随时停止发帖。
- Then you won't mind when your FaceShack door
- 那么你不会介意当你的FaceShack门
closes forever
永远关闭
after I tell the whole school
在我告诉整个学校
that BoCo Yolo is a fraud.
BoCo Yolo是个骗子之后。
- Go ahead and try.
- 尽管试试。
But let me BoCo-splain something to you.
但让我来给你解释一下BoCo。
We've got the strong, personal brand now.
我们现在拥有强大的个人品牌。
So who do you think the people are gonna believe?
所以你认为人们会相信谁？
You? Or the BoCo?
你？还是BoCo？
- Touché.
- 说得好。
You know, it's too bad.
你知道，这太遗憾了。
Everybody loves BoCo,
大家都喜欢BoCo，
but since they don't know it's you,
但既然他们不知道是你，
you can never get any of that love.
你就永远得不到那份爱。
You'll never know what it feels like
你永远不知道那种感觉
to get the points...
得到分数...
and the wiggle waves...
还有摇摆的波浪...
like I did.
就像我那样。
Just in case I wasn't clear, it feels good.
以防我没说清楚，感觉很好。
[laughter]
[笑声]
Real good.
真的很好。
It feels so-- all: We get it!
感觉太... 我们都懂了！
- I want the points.
我想要积分。
- I want the wiggle waves.
我想要摇摆波。
- I want it all.
我全都要。
- Wait, but I thought we were just doing this to help Ricky.
等等，但我想我们只是为了帮助Ricky。
- Well, I mean, it started that way,
嗯，我的意思是，一开始是这样，
but it doesn't matter.
但现在已经不重要了。
We can never get any of it because BoCo's not real,
我们永远得不到任何东西，因为BoCo不是真的，
so the world's never gonna get to see him.
所以世界永远不会看到他。
- Hey, everybody!
嘿，大家！
BoCo just posted that he's gonna be revealing himself
BoCo刚刚发帖说他现在要在公共区域露面了！
in the common area right now!
在公共区域，他就要揭晓自己了！
- Okay, we have got to stop saying
好吧，我们不能再这么说
things are never gonna happen!
事情永远不会发生！
all: [chanting] BoCo! Yolo!
大家：[齐声] BoCo！Yolo！
[chanting stops]
[齐声停止]
Mae?
Mae？
all: Mae?
大家：Mae？
- Not anymore.
不再是了。
It's BoCo Yolo now!
现在是BoCo Yolo了！
all: [chanting] BoCo! Yolo!
所有人：[齐声] BoCo！Yolo！
♪ ♪
all: [chanting] BoCo! Yolo!
所有人：[齐声] BoCo！Yolo！
- Mae, what do you think you're doing?
- Mae，你觉得自己在做什么？
- Hey, I gave you people what you wanted.
- 嘿，我给了你们想要的东西。
Now I'm just giving these people what they want.
现在我只是给这些人他们想要的。
- Mae, you were the one who warned us
- Mae，是你警告我们这条路很危险。
about the dangerous road.
- 但是那些敲击...和得分...
- But the knocks... and the points...
- 还有那些摇摆...感觉很好。
and the wiggles... feel good.
还有那些摇摆...感觉很好。
Real good.
真的很好。
all: [chanting] BoCo! Yolo!
所有人: [齐声] 博科！优洛！
- Mae, what I'm about to do is for your own good.
梅，我即将要做的是为了你好。
Everybody! I have an announcement!
各位！我有一个公告！
Mae is not BoCo Yolo!
梅不是博科优洛！
[all gasp]
[所有人惊呼]
She couldn't be BoCo Yolo
她不可能是博科优洛
because the truth is...
因为真相是...
I'm BoCo Yolo!
我是博科优洛！
[all gasp]
大家惊讶地吸气。
- What are you doing?
你在做什么？
- Yeah, what are you doing?
是啊，你在做什么？
- Going solo Yolo.
独自一人，YOLO。
- Yeah? Well, two can go solo.
是吗？那我也可以独自一人。
She's not BoCo Yolo!
她不是BoCo Yolo！
I'm BoCo Yolo!
我是BoCo Yolo！
[all gasp]
大家再次惊讶地吸气。
- No... I'm BoCo Yolo!
不... 我是BoCo Yolo！
And they're called "Nickerdoodles"!
它们被称为“Nickerdoodles”！
- How do we know that any of you is the real BoCo Yolo?
我们怎么知道你们中任何一个是真正的BoCo Yolo？
- And that you actually did any of that crazy stuff
而且你们真的做了那些你在网上发布的疯狂事情？
you posted online?
也许他们应该做些疯狂的事来证明！
- Maybe they should do something crazy to prove it!
我不知道是谁说的，但这是个好主意。
I don't know who said that, but it's a great idea.
对！
all: Yeah!
对！说点什么。
- Yeah! Say something.
什么都行。我会做的。
Anything. I'll do it.
那将证明我是真正的BoCo Yolo。
That'll prove that I'm the real BoCo Yolo.
不，我会做。
- No, I'll do it. - No, I will.
- No, I will. Name anything.
- 不，我来。说个什么吧。
- Skydiving!
- 跳伞！
all: Anything else!
所有人：别的什么！
- No, we're good with skydiving.
- 不，跳伞就够了。
- I'm out.
- 我退出。
- Well, I would skydive,
- 嗯，我会跳伞，
but where are we gonna get a plane?
但我们在哪儿弄飞机？
- My dad has a plane.
- 我爸有架飞机。
all: Yeah!
所有人：耶！
- Uh... yeah, but we don't have any parachutes.
- 呃... 是的，但我们没有降落伞。
- The plane came with parachutes.
- 飞机上配备了降落伞。
all: Whoo!
所有人: 哇！
- Yeah, but he probably doesn't have any kid sizes.
- 是的，但他可能没有适合小孩的尺寸。
- Actually, he just opened a kid-friendly skydiving school.
- 实际上，他刚开了一家儿童友好的跳伞学校。
[all cheering]
[所有人欢呼]
He's got an opening this Saturday.
他这周六有个空档。
- Ooh, I've got a thing this Saturday.
- 哦，我这周六有事。
- Yeah, I mean, is there any way
- 是的，我是说，有没有办法
we can just settle this right now?
我们现在就能解决这个问题？
- Like, closer to the ground?
- 比如，离地面更近一点的方式？
- Walk on hot coals!
- 赤脚走过火炭！
Again, I don't know who said that,
再次声明，我不知道是谁说的，
but it's a great idea.
但这真是个绝妙的主意。
Since BoCo already did it once,
既然BoCo已经做过一次，
it shouldn't be a problem.
应该不成问题。
all: Yeah!
众人: 对！
- True, true, I would definitely walk on hot coals again...
- 确实，确实，我肯定会再次赤脚走过火炭……
if we had any, but since we don't--
如果我们有火炭的话，但我们没有——
- I've got hot tots!
- 我有热辣薯球！
Fresh out of the oven.
刚出炉的。
They'll do the job!
它们会派上用场的！
[laughter]
[笑声]
all: [chanting] Hot tots! Hot tots!
所有人：[齐声] 热土豆球！热土豆球！
- Uh, what's this for?
呃，这是干什么用的？
- Oh, you'll know.
哦，你很快就会知道的。
- Wait, hold on.
等等，稍等一下。
Let me just make sure these tots are hot.
让我确认一下这些土豆球是不是热的。
Oh, hot! Hot!
哦，热！热！
[yelling, sighing]
[喊叫，叹气]
- You were right. I did know.
你说得对。我确实知道了。
- Okay, on FaceShack, BoCo talked the talk.
好了，在FaceShack上，BoCo说了大话。
Now it's time to see who can walk the walk.
现在是时候看看谁能付诸行动了。
all: [chanting] Tot walk! Tot walk!
所有人：[齐声] 薯饼走！薯饼走！
- Okay, now's your chance to chicken out.
- 好了，现在是你退缩的机会。
- I'm not chickening out. - Yeah, me neither.
- 我才不退缩呢。- 是的，我也不。
all: [chanting] Tot walk! Tot walk!
所有人：[齐声] 薯饼走！薯饼走！
- Stop!
- 停！
Stop the tot walk!
停止薯饼走！
This is ridiculous.
这太荒谬了。
And it's all my fault.
都是我的错。
They only created BoCo to take me down
他们创造BoCo只是为了打压我
because I stole their stories and pretended they were mine.
因为我偷了他们的故事并假装是自己的。
[all gasp]
[众人惊叹]
- It's true. - All him.
- 这是真的。 - 都是他干的。
- So #RickyLife was actually #TheirLives.
- 所以#RickyLife实际上是#TheirLives。
But I learned something today, and it's a lesson for us all.
但我今天学到了一些东西，这是我们所有人的教训。
It's better to be less popular for who you really are
做真实的自己而少受欢迎
than more popular for something you're... not!
总比因为不是自己的东西而更受欢迎要好！
Hot tots! Hot tots!
热辣小薯条！热辣小薯条！
- You know what it's for, people!
- 你们知道这是为了什么，大家！
- [screaming]
-[尖叫]
- Ooh, I'm gonna get a lot of knocks for this one!
-哦，我为此会受到很多批评！
[camera shutter clicks]
[相机快门声]
[simultaneous knocking]
[同时敲击声]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
-♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪